[CLUB NAME]
I've finally found it,
the homepage of that girl's circle!
Eh? There's no page of their works!
This site is useless
???
??? (ano kata no toutou sato? subaraisa wo nani mo wakettenai)
I'll show each of you my ???
Hanging out with you today was really fun
Really? That's good
Tama-chan, you joined a good club
the senior members are nice
To be honest, I was worried at fist
You're like my papa, Yumine
I feel praised
Ah! Here's the manga you lended me.  It was really interesting
Really? Tell me what you thought of it later
I'm going to visit my club before class
Got it.  Do your best
Yumine has been my friend since elementary school
We parted ways in middle school, but now we're reunited
To me, she's a special friend
Lyrics?
Mm.  We've left the lyrics to others until now,
???
Knowing you, it's ??? (yapa fujikawa-san nara ??? tsukurichau no ka)
ahhh, konkai mada ii denpa orite kite nai na
jikai saku mo tanomu yo
ima iroiro neteru kouso tokoro dakara
/kagiri aru, jikan no naka de/
/anata no koto omou/
/anata no kokoro ??? chikara wo watashi ni/
oh? denpa kita ka?
I spent a lot of time reading manga yesterday
himeteru setsunai koigokoru komayaka ni egaita gensaku to iu ka
Hm?
Huh? Fujikawa-senpai?
/You were everything to me/
/If it's my fate to disappear/
/I loved you forever/
Oh? Yahoo, Honda-chan
Um, just now was...?
I wrote a poem to my senior
To your senior?
They're someone special to me,
shitanakute mo, seiippai mono wo tsukuritai natte
Senpai... I love you!
Those feelings will surely reach them!
Hm? Oh, why don't you help me?
Eh? Help you? Is that okay?
Of course!  ???
I don't understand!  Who do you mean by next?
Who?  Um....
Seki-san?
Forbidden love?!
I love you
If you do that your partner's a girl, ???
there will be rumors ???
Eh?  Anyways, can you visit from noon until homeroom? ???
Fujikawa-senpai's love-poem ???
I don't have any experience, but I'll do my best
honda-chan no fudan no koigokoro to ka banban oshiete hoshii na
otousama teki na
I love you
I love my papa!
That would turn out absurd! It would turn out complicated!
???
You think that's okay?